glubble.com 2010-05-30

# Glubble | Where Families Play!

### Glubble

## Privacy Policy

Glubble takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy informs you how Glubble collects, uses and safeguards information from you or your children (a “Member” or “you”) in using the Glubble Service. Please refer to the Kids’ Privacy Policy, below, for Glubble’s privacy policy for individuals under the age of 13 years old.

In this Privacy Policy, the following capitalized definitions are used, singular as well as plural:

Child Member(s): the child (or children) under the age of 13 for whom you create Child Accounts within your Glubble Family Account.

Communications Content: any information that is communicated between Members.

Feedback Information: any information that is reported to Glubble by filling in the feedback forms from the Service or Website.

Glubble: for purposes of this Privacy Policy, Glubble is a property of Glaxstar Corporation, inc., a corporation incorporated under the laws of the State of Delaware, USA.

Glubble Add on: the downloadable add on, or client, that is installed on your computer, which permits Glubble content to be viewed and enables Services.

User Account; any information about the User that is provided by the User for inclusion on the User�s Family Homepage profile.

Passive Information: Information that is necessary to provide you with the desired Glubble Services, such as a session ID token, source and destination addressing information, and the version of the software you are using.

Personal Data: any personally identifying information that Glubble possesses relating to you or any Child Account, excluding information in your User Account.

Registration Information: Information that is necessary to verify your identity and to provide Service, such as your name, billing information, credit card account and e-mail address and other information you may elect to provide to enhance and customize Glubble experience for you and any Child Members.

Service: means the services provided by Glubble and/or Glubble’s partners, as they may be extended or changed from time to time;

Website: the website located at www.Glubble.com.

Contents

  * What is Glubble and what services does it offer?

  * What information does Glubble collect?

  * How does Glubble use this information and for what purpose?

  * Under what circumstances does Glubble transfer Personal Data?

  * What are cookies? How does Glubble use them?

  * How far does Glubble’s responsibility extend?

  * How does Glubble protect your Personal Data?

  * Can this Privacy Policy be modified?

  * Kids’ Privacy Policy

  * What rights do you have and how can you contact Glubble?

1\. What is Glubble and what services does it offer?

Glubble is a property of Glaxstar Corporation Inc., a company established under the laws of the state of Delaware, USA. Its headquarters are located in Palo Alto in the Great State of California. Glubble offers the Glubble Add on and Services, which may be modified from time to time.

2\. What information does Glubble collect?

To obtain Services you will need to register and open an account. To comply with applicable law, children under the age of 13 are not permitted to open accounts, but must have a parent or guardian do it for them. When you open an account and use the Services, Glubble may gather and process the following information (see below for more information on each of these):

  * Registration Information

  * Member Profile (eg Family name)

  * Birthday dates of Family Members

  * E-Mail Addresses of Friends

  * Feedback Information

  * Passive Information

  * Your E-mail Address

  * Assessment Data

Glubble always collects Personal Data only from you, as the parent or legal guardian, and never knowingly from a Child Member. It will be up to the parent or guardian holding the Master Account to provide any personally identifying data for any Child Member.

3\. How does Glubble use this information and for what purpose?

Glubble’s primary purpose in collecting information is to provide you and any Child Members a personal Family Homepage and to provide you a safe, efficient and customized experience.

Glubble may use the information defined in this Privacy Policy to: provide the Services, provide customer support you request; resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; enforce the End-User License Agreement, Terms of Service and Terms of Sale; customize, measure, and improve the Glubble Add on, Services and Website content and layout; inform you about targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers (unless you opt out); compare information for accuracy; verify your age and identity; provide other services for you as described when Glubble collects the information. Additionally, Glubble may use your information as described below:

  * Registration Information.

You will need to register and provide Registration Information if you want to access or use Services.

To register, Glubble asks for information: your Family name and email and the name of the child(ren) and the birthdays of the Family Members. Glubble is not collecting personal information from a child.

  * User Account

Note: Personal Data that you provide on your User Account, or those you create for your Child Members, can�t be viewed by other users.

You can access your User Account from the menu in your Glubble Add on in order to view, correct, complete or remove information.

Child Members are not able to create or edit User Accounts.

  * E-Mail Addresses of Friends

You may wish to invite friends to join Glubble. If you use Glubble’s referral service, you will provide your friends’ e-mail addresses. The e-mail addresses and messages you provide will only be used for the purpose of automatically generating an e-mail message to these potential Glubble members and for no other purpose. These are immediately deleted after use. If you have requested to add that friend to your network when he or she joins Glubble, we will retain your friend’s email address so that when they join we can send them an invitation to join your network. We will not use their email address for any other purpose.

  * Feedback Information

Any information that you voluntarily submit in feedback forms is used for the purposes of reviewing the feedback and improving the Add on, Services and/or Website. Glubble reserves the right to utilize anonymous information for marketing purposes, for instance by displaying selected comments on the Website or in other communications. Glubble may from time to time ask you to provide information on your Glubble experiences, which will be used to measure and improve quality. You are at no time obliged to provide such information. Glubble will never disclose any personally identifiable feedback information to third parties (other than third parties who are involved in providing the Services, such as third party banking organizations and other providers of payment service where such feedback relates to those providers) without your explicit permission.

  * Passive Information

Passive Information is automatically generated. Glubble only uses this Passive Information, on an aggregated basis, to provide you with better service or for statistical information.

  * Your E-mail Address

Glubble respects the privacy of personal e-mail accounts and stores your e-mail addresses just as securely as other Personal Data. Your e-mail address will not be sold or given to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit permission. Glubble may use e-mail to send you messages about faults and Service issues or possible violations of the Software License Agreement, Terms of Service and Terms of Sale. Glubble reserves the right to use e-mail to notify you of any claims related to your use of Glubble Add on and/or Services, including without limitation claims of violation of third party rights.

Glubble may also use e-mail to keep you up to date with news about Glubble and its Services. If you do not want to be kept informed in this way by e-mail, please contact Glubble at support@Glubble.com.

  * Assessment Data

To track content usage and performance by Child Members, Glubble may collect and make available to you various Assessment Data. Assessment data is only accessible to you. Glubble may use Assessment Data in anonymous, aggregated form for marketing and business purposes. Glubble may also use Assessment Data to generate recommendations for Child Members.

4\. Under what circumstances does Glubble transfer Personal Data?

Except as provided below, Glubble will not sell, rent, trade or otherwise transfer any Personal Data to any third party without your explicit permission.

Glubble may disclose Personal Data of a User Account if Glubble believes in good faith that Glubble is required to do so by law, or that doing so is necessary to comply with legal process, law enforcement agencies, respond to claims, or protect our rights in or the safety of the Services, or to protect the safety or rights of other Users or Child Users.

Glubble may share Personal Data with its affiliates.

If Glubble offers contests, sweepstakes, and other similar features, the co-sponsor and/or the sweepstakes’ or contests’ administrators may have access to the Personal Data that you submit in your entry. If you do not wish for us to share such personally identifiable information with our sweepstakes or contest co-sponsors or administrators, please do not enter any contests or sweepstakes on Glubble.

To provide you with the Services, Glubble may sometimes, as necessary, share your Personal Data with partner service providers and/or agents, for example the third party banking organization or other providers of payment services. Glubble requires these third parties to take organizational and technical measures to protect your Personal Data and to observe applicable legal requirements. Please be informed that, notwithstanding this, in the unlikely event of an applicable governmental authority requesting Glubble or Glubble’s local partner responsible to such authority, to retain and provide Personal Data, or to install equipment in order to intercept User Communications, Glubble and/or its local partner will, to the extent required to do so by law, provide necessary assistance and information to fulfill such a request.

Glubble may use non-personally identifiable aggregated data and make it available to third parties. This aggregated data is used by Glubble or its partners to track traffic use, to gauge interest in certain features, to improve the Service or for other business or marketing purposes.

Personal Data that is collected may be stored and processed in any country in which Glubble and its affiliates and contractors maintain facilities. In this regard, or for purposes of sharing or disclosing data in accordance with this article 4, Glubble reserves the right to transfer and store your Personal Data outside of your country of residence. By using the Service you consent to any such transfer and storage of Personal Data outside of your country of residence.

As Glubble continues to develop its business, Glubble might sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, as well as in the event Glubble or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, Personal Data of Users will generally be one of the transferred business assets. Glubble reserves the right to include such Personal Data, collected as an asset, in any such transfer to a third party. Additionally, information about Members may be disclosed as part of a bankruptcy.

5\. What are cookies? How does Glubble use them?

Cookies are pieces of information that Glubble will transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable Glubble’s systems to recognize your browser. Cookies also enable Glubble to gain information about the use of its Website and to enhance the Website accordingly to the preferences of the users.

The Help option on the toolbar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Glubble’s cookies do not contain any identifying information.

6\. How far does Glubble’s responsibility extend?

The Website may contain links that will let you leave the Website and access other websites. Linked websites are not under the control of Glubble and it is possible that these websites have a different privacy policy. This Privacy Notice applies solely to Personal Data that is acquired on the Website or in connection with the Services, so Glubble urges you to be careful when you enter any personal information online. Glubble accepts no responsibility or liability for these other websites.

7\. How does Glubble protect your Personal Data?

Glubble takes appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect the Personal Data provided to it or collected by it. Your Personal Data can only be accessed by authorized employees or contractors of Glubble who need to have access to this data to perform their given duties.

Your registration information is encrypted or otherwise protect within a Glubble-controlled database or with a third-party service provider. Glubble seeks to safeguard the Personal Data you provide. As effective as encryption technology is, however, no security system is completely impenetrable, so Glubble cannot guarantee the absolute security of our database, nor can Glubble guarantee that any information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to Glubble over the Internet.

8\. Can this Privacy Policy be modified?

Glubble reserves the right to modify the provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time. Glubble will inform you of these changes by publishing the revised Privacy Policy at www.Glubble.com/legal/privacy. The revised Privacy Policy becomes effective thirty (30) days of such publishing, unless you expressly accept the revised policy earlier by clicking on the accept button. You agree that the express acceptance by you, or your continued use of the Glubble Service after the notice period of thirty (30) days, constitutes your acceptance of such revised Privacy Policy.

9\. How long is your Personal Data kept by Glubble?

Glubble will retain your Personal Data for as long as is necessary to: (1) perform the Service; (2) invoice you for your use of the Service and to maintain records until invoicing for the Service cannot be lawfully challenged and legal proceedings may no longer be pursued; (3) carry out Glubble marketing activities; (4) comply with applicable legislation, regulatory requests and relevant orders from competent legal authorities; (5) enforce the End-User License Agreement, Terms of Service or Terms of Sale; or (6) fulfill any of the other purposes detailed in this Privacy Policy.

10\. Kids’ Privacy Policy

PLEASE READ: This section of the Privacy Policy explains our information collection and use practices online for children under the age of 13. Glubble asks that you take the time to review our policy so that you can know exactly what information Glubble collects (and doesn’t) from children under 13. If you ever have any questions or concerns about this policy, please contact us at support@glubble.com.

a. What Information does Glubble collect from Children Under 13?

Glubble is firmly committed to protecting the privacy rights of children and specifically those rights as outlined by the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Glubble will not collect, use or save data from children under the age of 13 without the express consent of the child’s parent(s) or legal guardian(s).

Child Members can use the Add on, explore the Library, view Content, and participate in activities without submitting any Personal Data. Glubble will not ask a Child Member for any personally identifiable information, such as his or her name, e-mail address, phone number, etc.

When Glubble does collect information from Child Members using the Service, Glubble generally limits its collection to information that does not personally identify the Child Member. Glubble never collects more information from Child Members than is reasonably necessary in order to participate in the activity.

Assessment Data is collected when a Child Member is accessing or viewing content.

There may be some other activities that require Child Members to submit individually identifiable information in order to participate, such as promotions, sweepstakes or contests, or other activities such as newsletters or sending online postcards or e-mail messages. Glubble will notify you, via the e-mail address associated with your Account, and will identify your child to you by using his or her Screen Name that your child wishes to participate. Glubble will only collect your child’s name, mailing address, and other personally identifiable information from you, the parent, and not from your child. The information will not be used for any purpose and the information will not be used after the promotion or activity is complete. Co-sponsors and/or sweepstakes’, contests’ or activity administrators may have access to the personally identifiable information that is submitted. If you do not wish for us to share this personally identifiable information with sweepstakes, contest or activity co-sponsors or administrators, please do not enter your child in any contests or sweepstakes on Glubble.

Glubble won’t knowingly allow anyone under the age of 13 to register as a Member or otherwise submit more individually identifiable information than Glubble describes above, except with verifiable parental/legal guardian consent. If Glubble becomes aware that Glubble has inadvertently received individually identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, except as discussed above, Glubble will delete the information from our records as soon as Glubble discovers it.

Glubble also offers memberships to certain licensed pre-schools and other educational institutions, who in turn make the Service available to children under the age of 13. No individually identifiable information is collected from children who access the Glubble Service via these school Accounts.

b. How does Glubble use Personal Data of Child Members?

Glubble always collects Personal Data only from you, as the parent or legal guardian, and never knowingly from a Child Member. Glubble will only use that information for the express purpose for which it was collected and will only disclose that Personal Data as set forth below.

Except as set forth below, Glubble does not share Personal Data of Child Members with any third parties (except those parties that help us administer the Services) without a parent’s express consent. These third parties may not use the information for any other purpose, and have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the information.

Glubble may disclose Personal Data of a Child Member if Glubble believes in good faith that Glubble is required to do so by law, or that doing so is necessary to comply with legal process, law enforcement agencies, respond to claims, or protect our rights in or the safety of the Services, or to protect the safety or rights of other Members or Child Members.

Glubble may share Child Member Personal Data with its affiliates.

Glubble may use non-personally identifiable aggregated data and make it available to third parties. This aggregated data is used by Glubble or its partners to track traffic use, to gauge interest in certain features, to improve the Service or for other business or marketing purposes.

Personal Data of Child Members that is collected may be stored and processed in any country in which Glubble and its affiliates and contractors maintain facilities. In this regard, or for purposes of sharing or disclosing data in accordance with this article 4, Glubble reserves the right to transfer and store Personal Data of Child Members outside of their country of residence. By opening a Child Account, you consent to any such transfer and storage of Personal Data outside of the Child’s country of residence.

As Glubble continues to develop its business, Glubble might sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, as well as in the event Glubble or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, Personal Data of Child Members will generally be one of the transferred business assets. Glubble reserves the right to include such Personal Data, collected as an asset, in any such transfer to a third party. Additionally, information about Child Members may be disclosed as part of a bankruptcy.

c. Tracking and Content Recommendations

If you are setting up one or more Child Accounts, you are encouraged to set up an unidentifiable, anonymous screen name for each Child Member. Glubble may give you the ability to track the Child Member’s use of the Service (which may include allowing you to see what Content the Child Member is viewing, reading, and learning and, where applicable, performance metrics), as well as receive content and other recommendations based upon the Child Member’s use and progress. Glubble may also make content recommendations based upon previous usage of the Services, as well as your child’s appropriate grade range.

11\. Parent’s Rights

Glubble wants you to be comfortable with what your child is doing when using Glubble. Therefore, you may contact us at any time regarding privacy questions or concerns, or to request to review what Personal Data Glubble has collected from you or about Child Members.

If you would like to exercise your right to view, correct, complete or remove your Personal Data, please contact Glubble at privacy@Glubble.com. Within a reasonable period of time and upon verification of your identity, Glubble will fulfill your request, provided Glubble will not act contrary to applicable legal requirements in fulfilling your request.

You may also contact us at any time to request that Glubble delete your or your Child Members’ Personal Data and/or refuse to permit further collection or use of your or your Child Members’ information. Glubble will take steps to ensure that any person contacting us for a child’s information is that child’s parent or legal guardian.
